tecadmin.net 2015-06-14

# Privacy Policy - TecAdmin.net

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at rahul.kumar1099@gmail.com.  
At tecadmin.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by tecadmin.net and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, tecadmin.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons 

tecadmin.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on tecadmin.net.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to tecadmin.net and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Chitika  
Qadabra  
Infolinks  
adf.ly

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on tecadmin.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

tecadmin.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. tecadmin.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Mailing list

Visitors are invited to join our mailing list. No information, except an e-mail address is required for this. In addition, a confirmation from the email address is required, to prevent anyone from subscribing someone else without permission. Subscription to our mailing list will not start until confirmation is received. Requests to be removed from the mailing list will result in deletion of the email address.

All the information provided or collected by us will only be used within tecadmin.net and will not be sold, rented, loaned or traded with a third party, except where required by law. While this information is stored in database and files on server, So tecadmin.net will not be responsible for any hacking attempt that may lead to the data being compromised.

If offensive content is posted or sent anywhere on or to tecadmin.net or a visitor engages in any disruptive behavior on tecadmin.net, we can use whatever information is available to stop such behavior. This may involve informing relevant third parties such as employers, web hosting service provider, e-mail/Internet providers and law enforcement agencies about the content and behavior.

## Analytics

Tecadmin.net uses google analytics and wordpress.com stats for gathering the visitors information only.

**Last updates on: May 12, 2014, 8:55 AM IST**
